blinko.co.za 2009-08-06

# BUONGIORNO.COM - Press Room

## Buongiorno Group corporate website

This statement relates to our privacy practices in connection with this website. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites. Any external links to other websites are clearly identifiable as such.

**General statement**  
Buongiorno S.p.A. fully respects your right to privacy, and will not collect any personal information about you on this website without your clear permission. Any personal information which you volunteer to Buongiorno S.p.A. will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality, strictly in accordance with the Italian Data Protection Legislation (D.lgs 196/2003). 

**Collection and use of personal information**  
Buongiorno S.p.A. does not collect any personal data about you on this website, apart from information which you volunteer (for example by e-mailing us or by using our online feedback form). Any information which you provide in this way is used by Buongiorno S.p.A. only in line with the purpose for which you provided it.  
**Collection and use of technical information**  
This website does not use cookies, apart from temporary "session" cookies which enable a visitor's web browser to remember which pages on this website have already been visited. 

Technical details in connection with visits to this website are logged by us and/or our internet service providers for our statistical purposes. No information is collected that could be used by us to identify website visitors. The technical details logged are confined to the following items: 

  * the IP address of the visitor's web server
  * the top-level domain name used (for example .it, .com, .de, .es)
  * the previous website address from which the visitor reached us, including any search terms used
  * clickstream data which shows the traffic of visitors around this web site (for example pages accessed and documents downloaded)
  * the type of web browser used by the website visitor.

Buongiorno S.p.A. will make no attempt to identify individual visitors, or to associate the technical details listed above with any individual. It is the policy of Buongiorno S.p.A. never to disclose outside its Group such technical information in respect of individual website visitors to any third party (apart from our internet service providers, which records such data on our behalf and which is bound by confidentiality provisions in this regard), unless obliged to disclose such information by a rule of law. The technical information will be used only by Buongiorno S.p.A. and its Affiliates, and only for statistical and other administrative purposes. You should note that technical details, which we cannot associate with any identifiable individual, do not constitute "personal data" for the purposes of the Data Protection Legislation.
